<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- author: joseph2.coverdale@live.uwe.ac.uk -->
<!-- Data Security Discussion -->

<Report>
<title> Data Security Discussion </title>
    <p> I have chosen to talk about Confidentiality, Integrity, Utility and Availibility </p>
    
    <p> If the web application that we have built was to be deployed then there would need to be an administrator put in place, this is because our site uses a database to display an RSS feed. 
        The RSS feed contains a dataset from our SQL database, the data held in our database is for places of interest in Exeter and Rennes. 
        This could be administrated by setting up a log in system which allows a user to gain access to viewing it, but if this happened then we would need to prepare to protect the users data as somebody hacking in 
        and reviling somebody’s data could breach confidentiality.
        For our web application to have integrity the site and pages will need to be consistent, this means that each page we have on our site will need to have a similar layout and design. 
        The data that is kept on the site needs to be modified only when authorised, this is because if there are any types of unauthorised modifications then our site will breach data integrity. 
        A data integrity breach could happen when one or multiple lines in the RSS feed show inaccurate data for example, 
        if I looked in the feed for Exeter and saw a piece of data talking about Rennes then this would make it inconsistent which is a breach, we would tackle this by ensuring each piece of information is kept authentic. 
        Our website has usefulness because it displays the data regarding the weather for each city and different comments about places of interest, 
        but if the database went down which resulted in a loss of these then there would be a breach of utility. A way of tackling utility is by finding out how effiecnetly designed the site is for exmaple,
        can a user find there destination is less clicks? this will be discovered through testing. There would need to be procedures set in place to ensure that our database and other system are kept up, 
        and running to make sure everything on the site is kept present and displayed. Another example of why the database will need to be protected is what if somebody went on the site to view the places of interest for Rennes
        but the server was down, this would cause the access of the information to be denied. Having this information denied creates a denial of serve attack which causes a breach of availability. 
    </p>
</Report>